export const data = {
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What does TS stand for in TypeScript?",
            "options": [
                "TypeScript",
                "TypeStyle",
                "TypedScript",
                "TypeScripting"
            ],
            "correctOption": "TypeScript"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which keyword is used to declare a strongly-typed variable in TypeScript?",
            "options": [
                "let",
                "var",
                "const",
                "type"
            ],
            "correctOption": "let"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the purpose of the 'interface' keyword in TypeScript?",
            "options": [
                "To declare a class",
                "To create a new type",
                "To define a function",
                "To declare a variable"
            ],
            "correctOption": "To create a new type"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which loop is used for iterating over the elements of an array in TypeScript?",
            "options": [
                "for loop",
                "while loop",
                "do-while loop",
                "for...of loop"
            ],
            "correctOption": "for...of loop"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the purpose of the 'class' keyword in TypeScript?",
            "options": [
                "To define a function",
                "To declare a variable",
                "To create a new type",
                "To define a class"
            ],
            "correctOption": "To define a class"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which keyword is used to indicate that a variable may have a null or undefined value in TypeScript?",
            "options": [
                "nullable",
                "optional",
                "undefined",
                "null"
            ],
            "correctOption": "nullable"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the purpose of the 'try...catch' statement in TypeScript?",
            "options": [
                "To declare a function",
                "To handle exceptions",
                "To create a loop",
                "To define a variable"
            ],
            "correctOption": "To handle exceptions"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which operator is used for strict equality in TypeScript?",
            "options": [
                "===",
                "==",
                "!==",
                "=*="
            ],
            "correctOption": "==="
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the purpose of the 'namespace' keyword in TypeScript?",
            "options": [
                "To create a new variable scope",
                "To define a class",
                "To organize code into modules",
                "To declare a function"
            ],
            "correctOption": "To organize code into modules"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which built-in object is used for handling and manipulating dates in TypeScript?",
            "options": [
                "Date",
                "Time",
                "Clock",
                "Calendar"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Date"
        }
    ]
}
